showmelocal.com 2019-06-25

# ShowMeLocal.com - Privacy Policy

#### Collection and Use of Personal Information 

We collect the following personal information from you: 

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number 
  * Billing Information such as credit card number, and billing address 
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name, account number, password
  * Preferences Information you provide such as product or content interests, or communication or marketing preferences
  * Usage activity about how you interact with us such as purchase history, what content you viewed, and which areas of our site you visited

We also collect the following information from you: 

  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type
  * Demographic information such as household income, age, education, gender, interests, and zip code

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system. We use this information to: 

  * Fulfill your order
  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Assess your needs to determine suitable products or services
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you a newsletter
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Administer contests and sweepstakes you entered, and notify you if you won
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Conduct research and analysis
  * Respond to your questions and concerns
  * List you in our publicly accessible member directory. If you do not want to be listed in our directory contact us at support@showmelocal.com

**Choice/Opt-Out**   
You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at support@showmelocal.com. 

Social Features 

We enable you to create a profile, and share information such as messages, photos, and videos with others within your network. We cannot control the actions of others with whom you may choose to share your pages and information. Also we cannot guarantee that the content you post on our site will not be viewed by others outside your network. Information Obtained from Third Parties 

If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us. 

#### Disclosure to Third Parties 

We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.   
We may disclose your personal information 

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process< when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request, if ShowMeLocal Inc. is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

We share your personal information with other companies so that they can market their products or services to you. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at support@showmelocal.com. 

#### Tracking Technologies 

We or a third party contracted by us may use technologies such as cookies, Web beacons, or scripts to gather information about how you and others interact with our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific areas or features within our site and which links or ads they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used, improve our marketing efforts, and provide content and features that are of interest to you.   
We use Google AdSense to serve ads on this site. When you view or click on an ad a cookie will be set to help better provide advertisements that may be of interest to you on this and other Web sites. You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Google's Advertising and Privacy page: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

#### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you provide sensitive information (such as a credit card number) to us, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at support@showmelocal.com 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at support@showmelocal.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

#### Other Information

Our Web site includes third party hosted widgets, which are interactive mini-programs that run on our site to provide single-purpose services (e.g. sharing of articles, videos, etc.). Personal information, like your email address, may be collected and cookies may be set so the widget can work properly. The information through the widget is subject to the widget provider’s privacy policy. 

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at support@showmelocal.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so. 

**Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at support@showmelocal.com. 

**Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. 

#### Cookie Poilicy

Please review our cooking policy here. 

#### Feedback

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:   
ShowMeLocal Inc.  
1733 Sheepshead Bay Road, Suite 18  
Brooklyn, NY 11235   
United States  
Email: support@showmelocal.com 

Copyright © 2006-2019 **SHOWMELOCAL Inc.** \- All Rights Reserved. | [Made in NYC](https://nytech.org/made)

SHOWMELOCAL®.com is Your Yellow Pages and Local Business Directory Network

SHOWMELOCAL® is a registered trademark of ShowMeLocal Inc.
